http://www.fundraiseralley.com/privacy-policy/

Search for:
Privacy Policy
Who We Are:
We are FundraiserAlley.com – an online only business featuring products for fundraising.
Our Privacy Policy:
We do not collect any customer information directly on this website. However, our products are sold through affiliate websites and there are links on our pages that will  take you to their website. Those websites may collect data from you. Also, we have share buttons that may collect your data. These are all listed below, with a link to each privacy policy.
1. ABCFundraising.com
As a ABC Fundraising® Representative, I offer their products on this site. Some product links my take you to their website for purchase. They may collect information from you regarding your purchase or to send you a free info guide. You can see their privacy policy here: ABC Fundraising Privacy Policy
2. Fundraising.com
Our affiliate, Fundraising.com, may collect data if you click over to their site from a link on this site. The site will appear as Fundraiser Alley, but it is a separate, partner site. You can see their privacy policy here: Fundraising.com Privacy Policy.
3. Amazon.com
We are also an affiliate with Amazon.com. Some of our links will take you to their site. You can see their Privacy Policy here: Amazon Privacy Policy
Also, we include share buttons on this site, which may collect information about you.  You can read each of their privacy policies using the links given below.
4. Share Buttons
Facebook Share official buttons:
We embed a Facebook widget to allow you to “like/share/recommend” our webpages. This widget may collect your IP address, your web browser User Agent, store and retrieve cookies on your browser, embed additional tracking, and monitor your interaction with the widget, including correlating your Facebook account with whatever action you take within the widget (such as “liking/sharing/recommending” our webpage), if you are logged in to Facebook. For more information about how this data may be used, please see Facebook’s data privacy policy: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update
Twitter Tweet official button:
We use a Twitter Tweet widget at our website. As a result, our website makes requests to Twitter’s servers for you to be able to tweet our webpages using your Twitter account. These requests make your IP address visible to Twitter, who may use it in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://twitter.com/en/privacy#update
Pinterest Save official button:
We use Pinterest Save widget at our website to allow you to pin images to Pinterest from our webpages. These requests may track your IP address in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy
Fundraising Products
Auntie Anne's Pretzels
Bake Sale Ideas
Beef Jerky
Canada
Candy
Candy Bar Kits
Carnival
NEW Products!
What Is a Web Store Fundraiser?
